("A Day in the Life")
♪ I read the news today, oh boy ♪
♪ About a lucky man who made the grade ♪
♪ And though the news was rather sad ♪
♪ Well, I just had to laugh ♪
♪ I saw the photograph ♪
♪ He blew his mind out in a car ♪
♪ He didn't notice that
the lights had changed ♪
♪ A crowd of people stood and stared ♪
♪ They'd seen his face before ♪
♪ Nobody was really sure if he
was from the House of Lords ♪
♪ I saw a film today, oh boy ♪
♪ The English army had just won the war ♪
♪ A crowd of people turned away ♪
♪ But I just had to look ♪
♪ Having read the book ♪
♪ I'd love to turn you on ♪
♪ Woke up, fell out of bed ♪
♪ Dragged a comb across my head ♪
♪ Found my way downstairs
and drank a cup ♪
♪ And looking up, I noticed I was late ♪
♪ Found my coat and grabbed my hat ♪
♪ Made the bus in seconds flat ♪
♪ Found my way upstairs and had a smoke ♪
♪ And somebody spoke and
I went into a dream ♪
♪ Ah I read the news today, oh boy ♪
♪ Four thousand holes in
Blackburn, Lancashire ♪
♪ And though the holes were rather small ♪
♪ They had to count them all ♪
♪ Now they know how many holes it takes ♪
♪ To fill the Albert Hall ♪
♪ I'd love to turn you on ♪